Problem?
This is the worst cobbler I've ever eaten.
It tastes like it's made of actual ground-up shoemaker.
Amusing. A play on the two meanings of "cobbler."
Hey   guys. Guess who I found at LAX?
My baby sister Priya.
Excuse me   I object.
You propose a guessing game
yet you don't give me enough time to guess.
For the record   I was going to say:
"Your sister Priya."
Oh   Sheldon. You haven't changed a bit   have you?
Why would I change?
The hope has been that
you'd eventually bend to public opinion.
So   Priya   what brings you back to L.A.?
I have a one-day layover on my way to Toronto.
Corporate merger.
Can you believe it?
Little Priya's one of the lead attorneys
for the biggest car company in India.
Given that when we met her   she was finishing law school
and planning an internship at a large Indian car company
it's actually extremely plausible.
And your poll numbers just keep dropping.
I want to catch up with all of you
but first I really must visit the loo.
I'm going   too; I'll show you where it is.
All right   this goes without saying
but I'm just going to say it anyway.
Hands off my sister.
Why would I touch her? She's covered with airplane germs.
I'm so not talking to you. I'm talking to him.
- Hey. I've got a girlfriend now.  - Oh   please.
My sister's much hotter than your girlfriend
and you know it.
Let's just agree they're both hot.
But dude   that's my sister you're talking about!
Okay   forget who's hotter.
The first time Priya came to L.A.   Leonard and I made a pact
out of respect to our friendship and to you
that neither of us would hit on her.
Did you pinky-swear?
Yes.
Okay   then.
Cobbler. I'm still laughing.
It's really nice to see you again   Leonard.
Yeah. It's good to see you   too.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Whoa   whoa   whoa   whoa   whoa!
Okay.
So you got any special plans with your sister?
Oh   not really. Just hang out.
I always tell people   "If you have only one day
in Los Angeles   make it a train day."
Train day?
The fun starts with brunch at Carney's in Studio City
a hotdog stand in a converted railroad dining car.
Next stop   Travel Town
an outdoor museum featuring 43 railroad engines
cars   and other rolling stock from the 1880s to the 1930s.
And   finally   we're off to the glitz and glamour of Hollywood
for dinner at--that's right-- the Hollywood Carney's
a hotdog stand in a different converted railroad dining car.
I don't think we're going to do that.
Well   then apparently you hate fun.
Priya's not back yet?
Well   I guess that's not unusual.
Women   men   the whole sitting-standing deal.
So what are we talking about?
Uh   my plans with Priya.
He rejected Train Day.
Did you make it clear that it's two different train cars
turned into hotdog stands?
Abundantly.
I guess he just hates fun.
That's what I said!
Okay   so... what's new with you guys?
I have a girlfriend now.
Hey   good for you!
Yeah   I just want to put it out there
in case I inadvertently
squirt any pheromones in your direction.
Happy?
So   Priya   what are your plans while you're here?
I don't know. I just have the one day.
Do you like trains?
Not particularly.
You might as well just wait at the airport for your flight.
"You are in a forest.
"There is quicksand to the west
a path leads to the east."
Go east.
"An iron gate blocks your way."
Open gate.
"It's locked."
Hmm.
Well   so much for that.
It's getting pretty late. How come you're still up?
I found an emulator online that lets you play classic text-based
computer games from the 1980s.
That's pretty cool.
Oh   yes. It runs on the world's most powerful graphics chip:
imagination.
You've really got to get out more.
Go north.
"You can't go that way."
Go west.
"A troll blocks your passage."
Okay. Fasten your seatbelts.
Kill troll.
"With what?"
With sword.
"You don't have the sword."
Good golly   it's as if it's actually happening to me.
Raj finally went to bed.
Sheldon's still up.
You said he goes to bed at 9:00.
Yeah   he does   but he got caught up in a computer game and...
Hit troll with axe!
My   this is one tough troll.
Can't you get rid of him?
If the past is any indication   no.
Leonard   I'm trapped in quicksand!
The axe is dragging me down!
Drop axe!
Drop axe   brilliant!
Give me a minute.
- Sheldon. - Hold on.
Trying to figure out how to get the bucket
so I can carry the mud past the dragon.
- Sheldon   you need to work in the morning. - I know!
Well   then bed   mister!
Five more minutes!
Really?
You're going to risk getting sleepy in the middle of your
thermodynamic fluctuations seminar?
You know what happens when you yawn in public.
Everyone will see my oddly shaped uvula.
You don't want that   do you?
No.
But it's a shame our society mocks the differently uvulated.
Who was at the door?
Uh   building manager.
They have to fix a pipe
so the water'll be off tomorrow from noon to 2:00.
That's unacceptable.
We're supposed to be given written notice.
Well   no   it doesn't matter-- we'll be at work.
What if I spill tomato soup on my shirt
and have to come home to change
only to find there's no water for an enzyme soak?
Bifurcated uvula   Sheldon!
I'll have the chicken noodle. Good night!
We're going to have to be very quiet.
I know how to get the bucket!
I can turn the axe around
and use the handle to reach it.
Let's see.
Go north.
"You are in a forest."
"You are in a forest." Oh dear   I believe I'm lost.
Well   I'll just have to get a fresh start tomorrow.
No   no   no! You just took a wrong turn.
You just need to map it out.
Come on   I'll help you.
So you stopped at the stream   and you turned north three times?
Yes.
You're right. You're lost. Good luck.
Leonard. Wake up.
Huh? Wh-- Sorry.
For what?
I don't know. When I'm in bed with a girl   it's just--
it's my go-to response.
It's 6:00. I have to get back to Raj's
before he wakes up and realizes I'm gone.
Oh. Right. Sure.
I wish you could stay in L.A. a while longer.
Mmm   me   too.
You know   I was thinking
there are some great research facilities in India.
Where are you going with this   Leonard?
Well   I'm just saying   you know   I don't have any real ties here
so if I were to move to New Delhi   we could   you know--
go out.
Leonard   didn't we have this conversation five years ago?
Well   yes   but...
things have changed.
You know   you're older   I'm older--
Look   no more superhero bed sheets.
Sweetheart
just because we have fun when I come to town doesn't mean
I want to have a serious relationship.
- It doesn't? - Mm-mm.
And besides   I could never bring a white boy home to my parents.
They'd have a cow.
Which is a much bigger deal in India.
I'm not that white.
My great-great-grandmother was half Cherokee.
I know that's not the right kind of Indian   but it is something.
You're funny.
Leonard?
What?
I heard a woman laughing.
Oh   uh   yeah. I was trying to see if I could laugh as a woman.
Oh! Well   good job. Quite convincing.
I smell perfume.
Air freshener.
And is that lipstick on your cheek and neck?
Rash. That's a bad rash.
My sympathies.
I'm no stranger to the crimson scourge that is dermatitis.
Can I interest you in a topical steroid
from my lotion and unguent collection?
Uh   yeah   yeah   that sounds great.
Very well. I'm sure I can find something
that will help you ditch that itch.
Okay   he's in the bathroom. Let's go.
Do you prefer ointment or cream?
Cream.
With or without a numbing agent?
Without.
Really   Leonard?
There are no heroes when it comes to dermatitis.
Fine. With.
Prescription or non-prescription strength?
Use your best judgment.
Well   I think I have a nice 2009 AnaMantle HC.
It's usually indicated for acutely inflamed hemorrhoids
but it also goes nicely with non-mucosal body parts.
Sounds great.
Excellent choice.
Okay   hurry   hurry   hurry.
Come on   come on   come on.
Priya?
Good morning   Sheldon.
For shame   Leonard   for shame.
And to think   I was ready to waste
the last of my good hemorrhoid cream on you.
Making pretty good time   huh?
Is that really what you want to talk about   Leonard?
No.
What do you want to talk about?
Please don't tell anyone
I spent the night with Raj's sister.
There it is.
What if someone asks?
No one's going to ask if I spent the night with Raj's sister.
Perhaps   but they might ask me something else.
- Like what?  - Like
"Has Leonard betrayed any of his friends recently?"
Priya and I are both adults.
I didn't betray Raj.
In fact   you did   but I was referring to Howard.
What are you talking about?
April 12   2005.
Bob's Big Boy   Toluca Lake.
Raj had just introduced us to Priya for the first time.
She was enjoying the sweet taste of Hindu rebellion
in the form of a Bob's Super Big Boy hamburger.
In order to preserve your friendship
you and Howard made a pinky swear
that neither of you would attempt to woo her.
I had a patty melt.
Okay   fine   I betrayed Howard.
- And Raj.  - All right   and Raj.
And me.
You?
Violation of the Roommate Agreement's
overnight guest notification clause.
Okay   fine   I-I'm a horrible human being.
I'm the Darth Vader of Pasadena.
You're far too short to be Darth Vader.
At best you might be a turncoat Ewok.
My point is: Priya's gone and it would be much better
if no one else found out about us.
You mean you want me to keep a secret?
Yes.
You know I can't keep a secret.
You can if you try.
Think about it this way:
um   if I were Batman and you were Alfred
you'd keep that secret   right?
Why do you get to be Batman?
Because Batman has the secret.
Alfred has secrets   too.
- Like what?  - Alfred knows
that Barbara Gordon is Batgirl.
Which I've now just told to Batman.
See   I cannot keep a secret.
Ta-dah!
What?
Ta-dah.
It's short for...
Da-da-da-da! ?
Kind of busy here   Sheldon.
I know   that's why I shortened it.
What do you want?
I came to go over your alibi for last night.
What alibi?
You've asked me to lie on your behalf   and as you know
I am deeply uncomfortable with impromptu dishonesty
so I've provided you with an ironclad alibi.
You couldn't have spent last night with Priya
because you were with another woman.
Oh   I'm so sure I'm gonna regret this
but who was I with?
The fun-loving and morally loose Miss Maggie McGarry.
Oh   God.
You met her at Pasadena's most popular
Irish watering hole   Lucky Baldwin's
where Maggie spends her nights tending bar
with a head full of curls and a heart full of dreams.
"Leonard   call me if you are interested in coitus.
Sincerely   Maggie McGarry."
And if anyone were
to actually call that number   they will hear this.
Top of the morning to you.
You've reached Maggie McGarry.
Leave a message after the wee little beep.
It's pretty convincing   huh?
That wasn't even a real person.
And here is the clincher:
a lock of Maggie's flaming auburn hair.
Where'd you get that?
From an orangutan in the primate lab.
An orangutan?
Well   no one's going to run a DNA test on it   Leonard.
Honestly   you overthink everything.
Sheldon   I don't need an alibi.
Nobody's going to ask about last night
as long as you just zip your lip.
Thank you.
Now   don't worry   everything is going to be fine.
Hey.
Hey   Leonard   will you please tell Howard
my sister has never been attracted to him?
Come on   Raj
how am I supposed to know
who she is attracted to or was attracted to
or who she might be attracted to in the future?
And I have nothing to contribute
to this conversation.
Because I   too   know absolutely nothing
about Priya's preferences in male companionship.
And with that   I will re-zip my lip.
Hey   so what did you guys think
of the new episode of Caprica last night?
I didn't see it.
Didn't see it?
What were you doing?
Uh   I was out.
What   on Caprica night?
Yeah   I   uh   went for a drink.
Really   you?
Where   w-where'd you go?
To   uh...
Lucky Baldwin's.
Oh   I've heard of that place.
Isn't that Pasadena's favorite Irish watering hole?
Yes.
Did you meet
anyone interesting there
perhaps a promiscuous   redheaded barmaid?
As a matter of fact... I-I-I-I-I can't   I can't
I can't do it.
Sure you can   you're doing fine   it's very believable.
I'm sorry   Raj   but the truth is
I was with Priya last night.
Don't listen to him.
He's still light-headed from all the Irish whiskey
and pickled eggs in his system.
What were you doing with Priya?
I believe they engaged in coitus
but more importantly
if Leonard had not abandoned his story
would you have found it plausible?
You slept with my sister?!
Yeah.
How could you? We had a pact.
Excuse me   I think "How could you? She's my sister"
takes precedence over a five-year-old pinky swear.
May I point out
in a parallel universe   your friends are saying
"Maggie McGarry-- she sounds lovely."
Look   I-I admit it   I may have crossed a line here
but come on   Raj   your sister is a grown woman
and to her   I'm a forbidden piece of white chocolate.
I don't believe it.
This is a terrible betrayal of my trust.
No   w-w-would it help if I told you
that I offered her my heart   and she kind of stomped on it?
How hard did she stomp?
Very hard.
Okay   I'm good.
Well   Raj
I just want to say that I'd never betray your trust.
Unlike Leonard   I respect you.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Was it out of respect that you didn't tell Raj
about the time you dropped his iPhone in a urinal?
Dude   I put that thing on my face!
I think a more amusing violation of Raj's trust
is when Howard convinced him that foreigners give presents
to Americans on Thanksgiving.
Hey   I didn't see you giving back
your Snoopy snow cone maker.
That was all a lie?
This year's gifts are already wrapped.
And as long as we're talking about betraying our friends
how about the month Sheldon spent grinding up insects
and mixing them into Leonard's food?
Well   excuse me.
That was not a betrayal.
That was an experiment to determine
at what concentration food starts tasting "mothy."
You put moths in my food?!
For science.
I can't believe you kissed my sister with moth mouth.
Well   I can't believe you used Sheldon's toothbrush.
You used my toothbrush?
Not the brush part   just the little rubber thing
to pick food from my teeth and massage my gums.
Okay   I-I think it's safe to say
that we've all done some things
we're not particularly proud of.
But come on   we're friends.
Friends overlook each other's minor lapses.
For the record   Howard   I'm sorry that I broke our pact.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry about your phone
and Thanksgiving.
And while we're at it
you don't have to wash our clothes on the Fourth of July.
As long as we're apologizing
Sheldon   I'm   I'm sorry I used your toothbrush.
And I'm sorry...
but that behavior is beyond the pale
and cannot be tolerated.
We are no longer friends.
I got you a talking Thomas the Tank Engine for Thanksgiving.
With real puffing smoke?
Yes.
All right.
But I'm watching you.
Hey   you've got Snoopy out.
Can I have a snow cone?
Well   sure.
This is pretty good.
What flavor is this?
Guess.
- Papaya? - No.
- Guava? - You're so close.
I give up.
Mango caterpillar.
What are you doing?!
You said you liked it.